imgchili.net 2017-12-30

# imgChili » Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

When you sign up for an account with imgChili, we collect personal information from you including your email address and a password. 

We may also collect the URL from which you linked into our site, your IP address, and your browser type and version. All of which are collected in an anonymous manner without being linked to any of your personal information. 

User privacy is something we take very seriously at imgChili. We do not, and have never, sold or disseminated (except in cases where required to by law enforcement agencies) the personal information of our users to any parties outside of imgChili. We use account information for the purposes of creating and maintaining individual user accounts, contacting a user in case of a problem with their account, for statistical purposes, to administer our systems, and to provide technical support. 

## Terroristic Content / Child Pornography Policy

imgChili.net provides a multimedia platform on the Internet, permitting Users to upload and publish information (image files) of their own. In particular, imgChili provides users with a virtual storage place, enabling them to store images on our platform. 

We do not tolerate child pornography on imgChili. When made aware of child pornography, we will act expeditiously to remove any such images, and we will report such content to the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children (NCMEC) as well as Meldpunt Kinderporno op Internet. We also reserve the right to take any other actions, including cooperation with relevant law enforcement agencies, to assist them in identifying and prosecuting individuals who are involved in the transmission or dissemination of images containing child pornography. 

## Notice

For faster removal, please email us at [[email protected]](http://imgchili.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0d6e6263796c6e794d64606a6e65646164236e6260327e786f67686e793059687f7f627f647e79646e2d4e6263796863792d222d4e656461692d4c6f787e68) and / or [[email protected]](http://imgchili.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#4235232e2e3b022b2f25212a2b2e2b6c212d2f7d313720282721367f162730302d302b31362b2162012d2c36272c36626d62012a2b2e26620320373127)
